In this video, you'll learn how to bring shoppers to your Brand Store homepage using Sponsored Brands
campaigns.
While you can choose different landing page options for your ads, linking to your Brand Store allows
shoppers to discover everything you offer while seeing the elements that make your brand unique.
In your Brand Store Insights, you can measure shopper engagement from your Sponsored Brands ads
by tracking metrics like page views, visits, and sales per page by traffic source.
Step 1.
Create a sponsored Brands Campaign.
Create a sponsored Brands Campaign in product collection or video format.
Then set your Brand Store homepage as your ad landing page.
Step 2.
Select Engaging Creative.
Create a good first impression with engaging creative that draws shoppers to your store.
Choose between video ads that bring your products to life or product collection ads with lifestyle
imagery.
Video ads should be brief, around 20 seconds, and grab attention in the first few moments as they
autoplay in search results.
For product collections, use high-quality lifestyle images that show your products in real settings.
Our AI image generator can help create these visuals while maintaining your brand standards.
Step 3.
Write a Headline.
Add a headline that communicates your product's unique value and inspires trust.
Step 4.
Select your products.
Think of your ad creative as telling your product's story at a glance.
Feature bestsellers, highly rated products with three or more stars, or new launches in your creative.
Step 5.
Targeting.
Create separate ad groups or campaigns for targeting strategy to tailor your message for better
control.
If using keyword targeting, select your branded terms to help capture brand-aware shoppers.
When trying to reach new to brand shoppers, use category-specific and broader keywords.
Learn from shopper interests by using keyword themes and your search terms report to spot relevant
terms.
For product targeting, begin with relevant category groups refining those to match your offerings.
Step 6.
Craft a Compelling Brand Store.
Craft a compelling brand store that guides shoppers from your ads to purchase,
featuring clear navigation, authentic lifestyle imagery and your unique brand story.
By aligning your Sponsored Brands ads with your brand store homepage,
you create a cohesive shopping experience that introduces your brand and encourages return visits.
Put learning into practice.
Create a Sponsored Brands campaign driving to your homepage.
Watch our other two videos in this series to learn more ways to connect sponsored brands to your
brand store.